arcadia.edu 2019-08-29

# Privacy Policy | Arcadia University

x

Our website uses cookies to understand how you navigate our content and to give you the best browsing experience.

Please read our [Data Protection & Use Notification](https://www.arcadia.edu/data-protection-use-notification) to learn more.

### 

University Web Site Usage Policies

Access to and use of the Arcadia University Web Site is expressly conditioned upon agreement to the following policies and conditions:

### Copyright Statement

The text, graphics, photos, and other materials appearing on the Arcadia University Web site are the sole property of Arcadia University, Glenside, Pa., and are protected by copyright law or other intellectual property law.

Arcadia University gives visitors permission to copy documents and other materials on this Web site for non-commercial uses within an individual organization only. Distribution, retrieval, storage or other use for commercial purposes is strictly prohibited without prior written permission from Arcadia University.

### Warranty

While every reasonable effort has been made to ensure current and accurate information on this Web site, the information is provided "as is", "as available" without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, and does not constitute a legal contract between the University and any other person or entity unless otherwise specified. Information is subject to change at any time without prior notice.

Responsibility for content contained within personal home pages or Web sites to which the Arcadia University Web site links resides solely with the author of such sites. Arcadia University is not responsible for any errors that might appear therein. Moreover, views contained therein are strictly the opinions of the author and are not officially sanctioned by Arcadia University.

### Privacy Policy

Arcadia University collects two kinds of information on this site: (1) registration information that is voluntarily supplied by visitors to this site who enroll in the programs offered through Arcadia University and (2) tracking information that is automatically collected as visitors navigate through this site.

Arcadia University uses the information you voluntarily submit to us for the sole purpose of providing the service you requested. We do not share personally identifiable information about individual visitors with any other person or entity.

Arcadia University may also collect tracking information through the use of cookies, which place certain identifying information on your computer to facilitate your future access. Arcadia University uses the data collected from Web site visitor cookies in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information. Arcadia University generates reports about the volume of visitors, variety, timing and other non-personal statistical information about traffic to our Web site for internal use to provide a better site for our visitors. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent.

We use reasonable precautions to keep any personal information collected secure and follow industry-standard precautions and procedures in the transmission and storage of electronic data. Specifically, the Arcadia University Web site uses secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to process secure information allowing online users protection from interception of private information by any third party. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security resulting from an individual user's computer security failures. Arcadia University links to a variety of other Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy policies, security or how they may handle any user information they may collect.

Please e-mail [WebServices@arcadia.edu](mailto:WebServices@arcadia.edu) for more information.
